Center for Law and Justice; Records apap072
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Membership, 1992-1997; 2; 1 cubic foot (3 boxes)
  This series includes form letters from the Center soliciting membership and membership forms. Many of the membership forms include copies of checks paid to the Center for yearly dues. Many of the forms came with notes and letters to Alice Green expressing thanks and appreciation for all of the work the Center is doing. The majority of membership forms are from prison inmates in New York State.
  Arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted.
  - Membership Applications and Letters, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Membership), Folder 1)
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Membership Applications and Letters, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Membership), Folder 2)
  - Membership Applications and Letters, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Membership), Folder 3)
  - Membership Applications and Letters, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Membership), Folder 4)
  - Membership Applications and Letters, A-F, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Membership), Folder 1)
  - Membership Applications and Letters, G-M, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Membership), Folder 2)
  - Membership Applications and Letters, N-S, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Membership), Folder 3)
  - Membership Applications and Letters, T-Z, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Membership), Folder 4)
  - Membership Applications and Letters, A-H, 1997 (Box 3 (2-Membership), Folder 1)
  - Membership Applications and Letters, J-M, 1997 (Box 3 (2-Membership), Folder 2)
  - Membership Applications and Letters, P-W, 1997 (Box 3 (2-Membership), Folder 3)
- Capital District Community Conference on Crime and Criminal Justice, 1991-1994; 3; 1.33 cubic ft. (4 boxes)
  The Center for Law and Justice, Inc. began sponsoring an annual conference entitled Capital District Community Conference on Crime and Criminal Justice on May 18, 1991. The goal of the conference was to bring together law enforcement officials, human rights advocates, and community members to address a wide range of controversial issues concerning bias in the criminal justice system and its impact on people of color, women, children and the poor. The conferences were one-day events, with keynote speakers, educational workshops, and strategy sessions.
  Themes:
  1991 - Education, Mobilization and Change (May 18, 1991)
  1992 - Separate and Unequal: Racial Bias in Policing and the Courts (April 11, 1992)
  1993 - Effects of Prisons on Communities: Issues and Alternatives (April 24, 1993)
  1994 - Youth and the Law: Problems and Solutions (April 16, 1994)
  1995 - The Death Penalty: A Matter of Race (April 1, 1995)
  1996 - Criminal Injustice (April 20, 1996).
  Arranged alphabetically within each year.
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 1)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 2)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 3)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 4)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 5)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 6)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 7)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 8)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 9)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 10)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 11)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 1)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 2)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 3)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 4)
  - First Annual, 1991 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 5)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 6)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 7)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 8)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 9)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 10)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 11)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 12)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 1)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 2)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 3)
  - Second Annual, 1992 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 4)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 5)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 6)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 7)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 8)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 9)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 10)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 11)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 12)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 13)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 14)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 15)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 16)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 17)
  - Third Annual, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 18)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 1)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 2)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 3)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 4)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 5)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 6)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 7)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 8)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 9)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 10)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 11)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 12)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 13)
  - Fourth Annual, 1994 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 14)
  - Fifth Annual, 1995 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 15)
  - Sixth Annual, 1996 (Box 4 (3-Capital District Community Conference on Crime and), Folder 16)
- Subject Files, 1982-1984; 1990-1993; 4; 1.9 cubic ft. (6 boxes)
  Series 4 consists of official correspondence, both incoming and outgoing. The correspondence ranges from thank you letters and invitations for special events to personal letters to/from local agencies, universities, leaders and activists. There are a few letters from inmates in these files, however that kind of correspondence is almost entirely found in Series 5. The correspondence in the series is from 1990-1993. Other subject files include information on Albany Law School, CAARV (Community Action Against Racism and Violence), the Community Police Board, Dr. Green's doctoral dissertation, and a syllabus for a course entitled Law and the Black Community (a course Dr. Green was teaching).
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Albany Law School, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - CAARV, Community Action against Racism and Violence, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2-3)
  - Client Lists, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Community Police Board, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- Incoming, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence -- Outgoing, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence -- Incoming, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- Outgoing, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- Incoming, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- Outgoing, 1992 January-May (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- Outgoing, 1992 June-December (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- Incoming, 1993 January-June (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- Incoming, 1993 July-December (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- Outgoing, 1993 January-June (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- Outgoing, 1993 July-December (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- Incoming, 1995 January-April (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- Incoming, 1995 May-September (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- Incoming, 1995 October-December (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- Outgoing, 1995 January-June (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- Outgoing, 1995 July-December (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Doctoral Dissertation, by Dr. Alice Green, 1982 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Doctoral Dissertation cont, by Dr. Alice Green, 1982 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Flyers, Undated (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Jessie Davis -- Civilian Police Review Board, 1985 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Jessie Davis, 1984-1985; 1990-1994; clippings (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Jessie Davis -- Community Response to the Shooting, 1984-1985 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Jessie Davis -- Correspondence, 1984-1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Jessie Davis -- Fact Sheet Concerning Jessie Davis Shooting, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Jessie Davis -- Grand Jury Report, 1984 August 23 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Jessie Davis -- Justice for Jessie Davis Network, 1984-1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Jessie Davis -- Lawsuit -- Affidavit of Anthony V. Bouza, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Jessie Davis -- Lawsuit -- Affidavit of David Aloisi, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Jessie Davis -- Lawsuit -- Correspondence, 1992 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Jessie Davis -- Lawsuit -- Deposition, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Jessie Davis -- Lawsuit -- Memorandum of Decision and Order, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Jessie Davis -- Lawsuit -- Order to Show Cause, 1994 May 6 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Jessie Davis -- Police Brutality in Albany, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Jessie Davis -- Police Standard Operating Procedures (Re: Deadly Force and Mental Illness, 1979-1982 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Jessie Davis -- Press Releases and the Media, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Jessie Davis -- Public Hearing before the Albany Common Council, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Jessie Davis -- Scrapbook, 1984-1985 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    Photocopied from a scrapbook that was returned to the Center as per their request.
  - Jessie Davis -- Settlement, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Jessie Davis -- State of Settlement, 1994 June 20 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Law and the Black Community (AAS 530), 1992 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Legally Speaking Workshop Evaluations, 2000 April (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Rights of Ex-Offenders Workshops Evaluation, Undated (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Statistics, Undated (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
- Prisoner Intakes and Letters, 1988-1998; 5; 5.33 cubic ft. (16 boxes)
  Series 5 consists of prisoner intake files. The files contain letters from the prisoners to Alice Green or her staff. You can also find letters responding to the prisoners' inquiries and/or needs from Alice Green and her staff. The correspondence ranges from letters of introduction, explaining why they are/were incarcerated and what services or information they seek from the Center to Christmas cards. Some of the letters come from family members advocating on behalf of a loved one in prison. Most of those letters are from mothers or wives. The correspondence contains very personal information on the inmate and sometimes on the people they victimized or allegedly victimized, which is why the series is restricted.
  Arranged alphabetically by prisoners name.
  Access to the records in this series is closed to researchers. Please consult Curator of Manuscripts for more information.
- Newspaper Clippings, 1985-1995; 6; 2 cubic ft. (6 boxes)
  The Center for Law and Justice maintained clippings files about issues and events that affected the criminal justice system, especially as it pertained to race and the African American community. There are also clippings on the African American community as a whole, both locally and nationally. The clippings span from 1985 to 1995, though articles from pre-85 and post-95 may be found randomly throughout the subject areas. The subject areas include Affirmative Action, African American Families, African American Females, African American Males, African Americans, African Americans in Albany, African Americans in the Media, AIDS, Albany, Alternatives to Incarceration, Center for Law and Justice, Civilian Control of Police, Civil Liberties, Civil Rights, Community Policing, Courts, Crime, Crime Economics, Criminal Justice, Criminal Justice System and Race, Crime Prevention, Death Penalty, Death Row, Drugs, Education, Female Prisoners, Forfeiture Bill, Fourth Amendment, Grand Jury, Juries, Insanity Defense, Misconduct, NYS Legislature, Police Brutality, Poverty, Pre-Trial Release, Prisoners, Prisons, Public Defense, Race and Media, Race and Racism, Race and Racism, Schenectady, Tenants' Rights, Troy, Use of Force, Violence, and Youth.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Affirmative Action, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - African American Families, Undated (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - African American Females, Undated (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - African American Males, Undated (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - African Americans, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - African Americans, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - African Americans, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
  - African Americans in Albany, Undated (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - African Americans in the Media, Undated (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 9)
  - AIDS, 1985-1994 (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 10)
  - Albany, NY, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 11)
  - Alternatives to Incarceration, Undated (Box 1 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 12)
  - Center for Law and Justice, 1990; 1991 (Box 2 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Center for Law and Justice, 1992 (Box 2 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Center for Law and Justice, 1993 (Box 2 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Center for Law and Justice, Undated (Box 2 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - Civilian Control of Police, 1984-1989 (Box 2 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Civil Liberties, 1989-1993 (Box 2 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Civil Rights, 1990-1993 (Box 2 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
  - Community Policing, Undated (Box 2 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - Courts, Undated (Box 3 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Crime, 1985-1994 (Box 3 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Crime Economics, Undated (Box 3 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Criminal Justice, Undated (Box 3 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - Criminal Justice System and Race, Undated (Box 3 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Crime Prevention, Undated (Box 3 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Death Penalty, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Death Row, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Drugs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Education, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - Female Prisoners, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Forfeiture Bill, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Fourth Amendment, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
  - Grand Jury, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - Juries, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 9)
  - Insanity Defense, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 10)
  - Misconduct, Undated (Box 4 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 11)
  - NYS Legislature, Undated (Box 5 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Police Brutality, Undated (Box 5 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Poverty, Undated (Box 5 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Pre-Trial Release, Undated (Box 5 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - Prisoners, Undated (Box 5 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Prisons, Undated (Box 5 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Public Defense, Undated (Box 5 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
  - Race and Media, Undated (Box 5 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - Race and Racism, Undated (Box 5 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 9)
  - Race and Racism, Undated (Box 6 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Schenectady, NY, 1992-1994 (Box 6 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Tenants' Right, Undated (Box 6 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Troy, NY, 1992-1994 (Box 6 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - Use of Force, Undated (Box 6 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Violence, Undated (Box 6 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Youth, Undated (Box 6 (6-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
- Photographs, 1991-1995; 7; 0.2 cubic ft. (1 box)
  This series contains photographs of special events held and sponsored by The Center for Law and Justice. There are some notable people from the Capital District that are featured as speakers or being honored.
  Folder 1 includes a black and white photograph of Jonathan E. Gradess, Executive Director of the Defenders' Association. Gradess was honored with the Frederick Douglass Struggle for Justice Award in 1995. Included in the folder is a short biography of Gradess.
  Folder 2 contains 14 color photographs of participants from the Prevention and Empowerment Program (PREP).
  Folders 3 to 10 include 16 photographs of the Center for Law and Justice's first Capital District Community Conference on Crime and Criminal Justice. The event was on Saturday, May 18, 1991 at the Empire State Plaza Convention Center in Albany, New York.
  - Black and White Photograph of Jonathan E. Gradess, Executive Director of the Defenders' Association and 1995 recipient of the Frederick Douglass Struggle for Justice Award, given by the Center for Law and Justice, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Color photos of the Prevention and Empowerment Program, Undated (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - 1991 Conference (Box 1 (7-Photographs), Folder 3-10)
- Administrative Files, 1985-1998; 8; 0.17 cubic ft. (1 box)
  Series 8 is made of the administrative files of the Center. This includes annual reports, legal documents, certificate of incorporation, tax forms, financial statements and board meeting minutes. The documents are incomplete and there are several gaps in time for some of the files.
  - Annual Reports, 1994-2000 (Box 1 (8-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors, Undated (Box 1 (8-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1991-2000 (Box 1 (8-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Bylaws, Undated (Box 1 (8-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Center for Law and Justice, Inc., Undated (Box 1 (8-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (8-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Insurance, 1991 (Box 1 (8-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Legal Documents, 1990 (Box 1 (8-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
    (includes IRS forms, Certificate of Incorporation, etc.).
  - Mission, Undated (Box 1 (8-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
- Publications, 1991-2000; 9; 0.33 cubic ft. (1 box)
  Series 9 consists of a small number of Center publications including The Advocate. The collection of The Advocate is incomplete. There is also a folder of publications by others, relevant to some of the work done by the Center. The Advocate is a quarterly community criminal justice journal. First published in 1992, the Advocate serves to inform and educate the community about the criminal justice system and how it operates. Regular features include the demographics of the state prison population, significant local and national criminal justice news briefs, summaries of important legislation and court decisions, writings by prisoners, book and film reviews, and guest editorials.
  - Advocate, 1992-1996 (Box 1 (9-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Advocate, 1997-2000 (Box 1 (9-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Did You Know? Some General Legal Concepts, Undated (Box 1 (9-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Do We Need More Prisons?, Undated (Box 1 (9-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Newsletter Articles, 1991 (Box 1 (9-Publications), Folder 5)
  - On Your Own: Free Legal Information and Services in the Capital District, Undated (Box 1 (9-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Publications by Others, Undated (Box 1 (9-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Repairing the Breach: Key Ways to Support Family Life, Reclaim Our Streets and Rebuild Civil Society in America's Communities, 1996 (Box 1 (9-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Street Smart: Your Legal Rights on the Street, Undated (Box 1 (9-Publications), Folder 9)
  - To Protect and Serve? A Status Report on the Relationship between the Community and the Albany Police Department, 1998 June (Box 1 (9-Publications), Folder 10)